Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - P-S
        - Sweep - Got me movin', 2000; SR-27954; Sweep (Box 72)
          Catalog # RISE 088; A-side Matrix # RISE 088 A
          Rise
        - Sweet Apple - Sweet Apple, 1970; SR-27955; Sweet Apple (Box 72)
          Catalog # C 30238; A-side Matrix # PAL-30238-1A STEREO
        - Sweet Cookie - Do you wanna dance, 1987; SR-27956; Sweet Cookie (Box 72)
          Catalog # F-9657; A-side Matrix # (A) 1 G F-9657 A1 RE1
          Danya Records
          Walnut Creek, California
        - Sweet Inspirations - Hot butterfly, 1979; SR-27957; Sweet Inspirations (Box 72)
          Catalog # RS-1-3058; A-side Matrix # T1 RS-1-3058-BS-CT 1 FOR DAD JG
        - Sweet Talks - Do the beat, 1979; SR-27958; Sweet Talks (Box 72)
          Catalog # MK-82; A-side Matrix # MK-82 A-CT1 IT GK
          Ghana
        - Sweet Tee - On the smooth tip; As the beat goes on, 1988; SR-27959; Sweet Tee (Box 72)
          Catalog # PRO-7230; A-side Matrix # A-1 PRO-7230-A
        - Sweet Thunder - Sweet Thunder, 1978; SR-27960; Sweet Thunder (Box 72)
          Catalog # F-9547; A-side Matrix # F-9547-A-RE1 T
        - Swervedriver - 99th Dream, 1997; SR-27961; Swervedriver (Box 72)
          Catalog # ZER LP 1230; A-side Matrix # ZER LP 1230 A AABAJ
        - Swing - Swing, 1981; SR-27962; Swing (Box 72)
          Catalog # PA-24; A-side Matrix # 0-1 SM3-2 P-24-AS-SH-SP + SLM + 911 Precision Lacquer SM
        - Switch - Switch V, 1981; SR-27963; Switch (Box 72)
          Catalog # G8-1007M1; A-side Matrix # G8-1007M1-A-15A zsn 13 m BHF
        - Switch - Switch V, 1981; SR-27964; Switch (Box 72)
          Catalog # G8-1007M1; A-side Matrix # G8-1007M1-A-15A zsn 13 m
        - Swoosh - The hyped EP (disc one), 1997; SR-27965; Swoosh (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27966. Double album.
          Catalog # B2B12054; A-side Matrix # B2B-12054 A1
          Back 2 Basics
          Tipton, England
        - Swoosh - The hyped EP (disc two), 1997; SR-27966; Swoosh (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27965. Double album.
          Catalog # B2B12054; A-side Matrix # B2B 12054-C1
        - Syl Dopson And His Merry Boys - Kaiso vol. 2, 1974; SR-27967; Syl Dopson And His Merry Boys (Box 72)
          Catalog # RA 5040; A-side Matrix # RA 5040 A-2
        - Sylk 130 - Last night a DJ saved my life, 1997; SR-27968; Sylk 130; Britt, King (Box 72)
          Catalog # 44 78575; A-side Matrix # XSS 78575A-1A
        - Sylk 130 - When the funk hits the fan (disc one), 1997; SR-27969; Sylk 130 (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27970. Double album.
          Catalog # C2 67906; A-side Matrix # AL-68523-1D
          Ruffhouse Records
        - Sylk 130 - When the funk hits the fan (disc two), 1997; SR-27970; Sylk 130 (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27969. Double album.
          Catalog # C2 67906; A-side Matrix # AL-68524-1D
        - Sylvers - Showcase, 1975; SR-27971; Sylvers (Box 72)
          Catalog # ST-11465; A-side Matrix # FP ST1-11465-Z3 VS
        - Sylvers - The Sylvers, 1972; SR-27972; Sylvers (Box 72)
          Catalog # PRD-0007; A-side Matrix # PRD0007 MGS 2964 S REV P 1972 MGM RecoRDS INC
          Pride
        - Sylvers - Forever yours, 1978; SR-27973; Sylvers (Box 72)
          Catalog # NBLP 7103 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBLP- 7103-AS CP-1 AZ B 1
        - Sylvers - Bizarre, 1984; SR-27974; Sylvers (Box 72)
          Catalog # GHS 24039; A-side Matrix # GHS 24039 A-SH2 B-20188-SH2 SLM 8138 1-1
        - Sylvers, Edmund - Have you heard, 1980; SR-27975; Sylvers, Edmund (Box 72)
          Catalog # NBLP 7222; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7222-AS-RE-1 PR-2 AZ (PR)P
        - Sylvers, Foster - Foster Sylvers featuring Pat & Angie Sylvers, 1974; SR-27976; Sylvers, Foster; Sylvers, Pat; Sylvers, Angie (Box 72)
          Catalog # SE-4935; A-side Matrix # SE 4935-1 REV
          MGM Records
        - Sylvers, Fosters - Plain and simple, 1987; SR-27977; Sylvers, Fosters; Hy-Tech (Box 72)
          Catalog # ST-17240; A-side Matrix # ST-1-17240 Z-2 B-26628-22 AL-SP15624 1-1 AL-SP
        - Sylvers, Fosters - Prime time, 1990; SR-27978; Sylvers, Fosters; Hy-Tech (Box 72)
          Catalog # SP-5279; A-side Matrix # SPO-5279-A ES1 emw #07031
        - Sylvester - Stars, Body strong, 1979; SR-27979; Sylvester (Box 72)
          Catalog # D-135; A-side Matrix # 1-1 D-135A KENDUN-A
        - Sylvester - Step II, 1978; SR-27980; Sylvester (Box 72)
          Catalog # F-9556; A-side Matrix # 1-1 F9556A KENDU C KENDU-C
        - Sylvester - Sylvester, 1977; SR-27981; Sylvester (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27982. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 9160-9531; A-side Matrix # TLC 9160-9531-A
          Willowdale, Ontario, Canada
        - Sylvester - Sylvester, 1997; SR-27982; Sylvester (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27981. 2 copies.
        - Sylvester - Too hot to sleep, 1981; SR-27983; Sylvester (Box 72)
          Catalog # F-9607; A-side Matrix # A F 9607 A 1A S2 SXT
          Fantasy Honey Records
        - Sylvester - Living proof (disc one), 1979; SR-27984; Sylvester (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27985. Double album.
          Catalog # F-79010; A-side Matrix # F 79010 A KENDUN-D JGS
        - Sylvester - Living proof (disc two), 1979; SR-27985; Sylvester (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27984. Double album.
          Catalog # F-79010; A-side Matrix # F 79010 B X KENDUN-D JGS
        - Sylvester - Sell my soul, 1980; SR-27986; Sylvester (Box 72)
          Catalog # F-9601; A-side Matrix # X5 5 Ab F 9601 A-1B
        - Sylvester - All I need, 1982; SR-27987; Sylvester (Box 72)
          Catalog # M-1005; A-side Matrix # M-1005-A
          Megatone Records
        - Sylvester - Stars, 1979; SR-27988; Sylvester (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27989. Different discs.
          Catalog # F-9579; A-side Matrix # F 9579-A RE P2 1-1 KENDUN-D 376 JGS
        - Sylvester - I (who have nothing), 1979; SR-27989; Sylvester (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27988. Different discs.
          Catalog # D-129; A-side Matrix # 1-1 D-129-AL SP KENDUN-D
        - Sylvester - Mutual Attraction, 1986; SR-27990; Sylvester (Box 73)
          Catalog # 1-25527; A-side Matrix # HERbIE JR 1-25527-ASR1 SP 1-2
        - Synergy - Games, 1979; SR-27991; Synergy (Box 73)
          Catalog # PB 6003; A-side Matrix # PB-6003-A
          Passport Records
          South Plainfield, New Jersey
        - Syreeta - Syreeta, 1974; SR-27992; Syreeta; Wonder, Stevie (Box 73)
          Catalog # M6-808S1; A-side Matrix # A 1 D5RS 7655-1-RE1-01A KENDUN
        - System - Promises can break, 1984; SR-27993; System (Box 73)
          Catalog # DMD 743; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-46364-2
        - System - X-periment, 1984; SR-27994; System (Box 73)
          Catalog # 90146-1; A-side Matrix # ST WTG-835383-A 1-
        - Systeme 2000 - Bossou, 1986; SR-27995; Systeme 2000; Frères Déjean (Box 73)
          Catalog # JM 2011; A-side Matrix # 86-5 J M 2 01 1 A
          Speed-Records